Return of Ultraman
See you!
Troops.
The meteorite that fell onto Hiratsune City moments ago
destroyed at least 1,300 houses.
Nearly 16,000 people are missing or deceased.
Central Hiratsune City has been devastated.
This
is our current situation.
Orders To Fire MAT Arrow 1
Destroying buildings
With the tremor that erupts
From the cries of the monster
the giant monster
It opens with a roar
And fire pours from its mouth
Scorching all of the
surrounding fields
The city is in trouble
The fire is approaching
He has returned
He has returned!
Ultraman, Ultraman
Ultraman!
This is a digital simulation created using the
information from the Cyclops surveillance satellite.
Shown rotating is the meteorite, Lambda 1, that hit Hiratsune City.
As you can see
there's no sign of anything that fell off after entering the atmosphere.
Moving on.
According to this, the resulting impact
has almost entirely taken out central Hiratsune City.
Please look at this.
It's an enlarged map of Hiratsune city.
The 10-kilometer red area has been devastated.
The yellow area, destroyed.
However, there is still the outer areas
that could contain at least 5000 survivors, to take into consideration.
Hmmm.
Lambda 1 has a diameter of 60 meters
and an estimated weight of 130 kilotons.
Wait, that doesn’t add up.
Aren’t meteorites just masses of rock?
With a diameter of 60 meters…
Exactly
At the most, it should be about 600 kilos.
Take a look at this.
This is a live model of Lambda 1 sent to us from MAT
At a glance, it appears to be a typical meteorite
But
Upon further analysis of a cross-section from protruding section
there seems to be something inside with the diameter of 40 meters.
Also, while weak we observed signs of life.
Huh, a 40-meter cavity?
We’ll treat it as a meteorite.
Reporting the situation.
Lambda 1, separating.
It’s splitting into 3 and moving away.
We’re getting a strong signal of life
on top of brain wave activity.
It’s a monster!
It’s an invasion.
We are being invaded.
Lambda 1 is probably not a meteorite
but a capsule sent from space to take out Earth.
It’s likely that its actually a monster.
Yamaga
Imamura
Hayakawa
Take off immediately
in the MAT Gyro 1, 2, and 3.
Yes, sir.
Ibuki, prepare for takeoff in the MAT Arrow 1.
Contact the Earth Defense Force Headquarters.
Yes, sir.
We’re entering into
emergency level 1.
Captain
The EDF Headquarters concluded that
due to no survivors from the meteorite
the use of nuclear weapons is unavoidable
and thus we should move to emergency level 4.
Understood.
A monster that rode a meteor to invade.
I’ve got a bad feeling about this.
If space’s strongest monster, Kiruan, has returned
Hayakawa
Ah, yes!
We’re heading to Hiratsune City in 2 minutes
don’t have second thoughts now.
the 3 life-forms begin attacking
the ruins of Hiratsune City.
This is the current state of Hiratsune City.
Relaying the sensor's information.
Alright, Hayakawa.
Be careful out there.
Yes, sir.
Nothing much down there.
Just a bunch of moles, locust, and broken buildings.
What’s this?
Directly below is
a reading!
Yamaga!
T-The hydraulic system is at its limit!
I’m done for!
What is this thing?
Dammit!
Valcon sub-machine, ok.
Firing!
You ok, Yamaga?
Yeah, somehow.
The heat sources have fused together.
It appears to be a monster.
Understood.
Arrow 1, you’re cleared for takeoff.
Ibuki.
MAT Arrow 1 take off.
And Shingo
Be careful.
I know that dad.
Shingo
Stay safe.
Arrow 1 has taken off.
Gyro 1, 2, and 3
It appears the monster is in your vicinity.
Commence with the Napalm attack.
Napalm!
Captain.
Ibuki said earlier
there might still be somewhere around 5000
survivors in outer Hiratsune City.
Don’t think about it, Hayakawa.
Roger.
If that was a Kiruan underground
napalm won’t work.
Wait
even if I became Ultraman
could I win?
Did we get it?
Visual confirmation.
It's a monster.
Bringing it up on the display.
Dammit, what is this thing?
There’s no doubt about it, this is a Kiruan.
There’s an Arrow signal from above.
Team!
It’s Ibuki!
Ibuki, don’t underestimate it.
I got it.
Focusing at 50 to 60,000.
Target locked.
It appears effective.
Commencing the laser attack.
Shit, a barrier?
Come on!
Dammit, not enough energy.
Ejecting the battery pack.
I’m hit!
Ibuki!
Return of Ultraman
It’s been 20 hours since Lambda 1 landed in Hiratsune City.
As far as the monster is concerned, MAT was unable to find
a single effective weapon among their Earth Defense arsenal.
Now they can only obey the orders from EDF HQ, and wait.
An oppressive air fills the control room.
Yes, Captain Ibuki speaking.
Yes, understood.
Troops, I’ll relay the order from EDF HQ.
Today at 8 o’clock am, we will attack the monster, Lambda 1
with thermonuclear weapons.
We’ve entered into emergency level 4.
It will be impossible for anything to penetrate our defenses.
Our command center is currently moving 40 meters underground.
Imamura, take the nuclear bomb and transfer it to the MAT Arrow 1 Mk.VIII.
I, alone, will pilot for this attack.
Captain.
The nuclear weapons, at least stop the nuclear weapons.
There might still be survivors in Hiratsune City.
Ibuki might still be
Captain, please stop this.
Woah, Hayakawa, what are you doing?
Isn’t it obvious! I’m taking us out of level 4.
Hayakawa, stop!
We gotta stop him!
Let me go!
But it's coming!
Bastard!
Guys, don’t you understand what you’re doing?
Let go!
Stop this, Hayakawa!
This is our chance to avenge Ibuki!
But!
You won’t avenge your countrymen? Are you even human?
Confine him to his quarters
Roger!
Excuse us.
At that time, an unusually cold frost covered Hiratsune City.
I'm a human.
Or am I Ultraman?
Dammit!
Attaching thermonuclear weapons to MAT Arrow 1 Mk. VIII
Presently, MAT Arrow 1 Mk. VIII is preparing for takeoff with thermonuclear weapons
MAT Arrow 1 Mk. VIII, preparing for takeoff.
MAT Arrow 1 Mk. VIII, clear for take off.
MAT Arrow 1 Mk. VIII, taking off.
Are you even human?
An attack?
Block status report!
C block to D3 are -
It’s Ultraman!
W-What?
It’s Ultraman. Ultraman has appeared.
He’s heading straight for Hiratsune City.
Captain, fall back. Captain.
20 seconds until the target.
Lock, disengaged. Fuse, set.
Preparing to release.
Shingo.
Releasing!
Ultraman?
That’s
Shingo! He's alive?
Ultraman, good luck!
Shingo.
Shingo! Shingo!
Hey, Shingo, hang in there!
Shingo!
Shingo, are you alright?
Shingo! Hey, Hey!
Shingo, hang in there! Shingo!
Destroying buildings
With the tremor that erupts
From the cries of the monster
the giant monster
It opens with a roar
And fire pours from its mouth
Scorching all of the
surrounding fields
- Ultraman, keep going!
The city is in trouble
The fire is approaching
He has returned
He has returned!
Ultraman, Ultraman
Ultraman!
Ultraman! The nuclear weapon!
He doesn’t have long until it explodes.
Captain!
Ibuki, you’re alright!
I was about to make a terrible mistake.
Thank you, Ultraman.
Did Ultraman make it out ok?
He’s alright, I’m sure of it.
Don't worry, he's alright.
Now that it’s all over, I’m starving!
We’re going home.
Hayakawa.
Earth Defense Force, MAT member Hayakawa Ken, 21 years-old.
His true identity is Ultraman
as well as a human being.